mpowerplayer.com 2010-05-10

# Corp.Mplayit.com

## Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### MPOWERPLAYER, INC., PRIVACY POLICY

_This document was last updated March 7, 2005._

Mpowerplayer, Inc., (“MPP”) is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how MPP collects and utilizes your personal information when you use our products and services, including consumer software, such as the Mpowerplayer, Mpowerstore, Mpowerserver, and MPP developer resources. 

#### WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?

MPP collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. We will never rent or sell any of the personally-identifiable information we collect from you to third parties, and will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless such sharing is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

#### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

You must open an account or complete an online registration with MPP to download or purchase MPP products and services, including free trials. Information gathered during the registration or account creation process, or during access to particular products and services, may differ based on the nature of the product or service. Information that you provide when registering or creating an account, or accessing or using your account or the MPP products or services associated with your account, may include: name and email address; billing information; information concerning software downloaded, products and content purchased, accessed, and/or downloaded through MPP products or services; location information (such as zip code or postal code and country); computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); the IP Internet (IP) address and URL of the Website that sent you to the MPP registration page; the types of peripherals used by MPP products on your computer (to ensure that you have access to the latest fixes and patches for full compatibility with these devices); demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, content preferences and personalization information); and whether you logged into or out of an MPP service, or changed your password or billing information. 

We will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as set forth below. 

#### HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

MPP understands that it is a privilege to have you as a customer and is committed to protecting your personal information. We use the following controls to protect your personal information: 

  * Use of secure connections using SSL to safeguard personal information when transmitted from your Web browser to MPP; 
  * Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information; 
  * Use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as credit card numbers and user names; 
  * Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do; and 
  * Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information. 

#### HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

MPP uses your personal information to: 

  * Deliver to you and bill you for MPP products and services, and communicate with you concerning your account and customer service issues. This may include verifying authorization of credit card usage before any purchase of premium content or services; 
  * Verify access rights to premium content or other access-restricted services and software, including for the purpose of supporting digital rights management software; 
  * Improve our software and services by providing personalized content recommendations, language and location customization, and/or personalized help and instructions; 
  * Determine if you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products, and provide information concerning compatibility and interoperability to you; 
  * Track content accesses and downloads for the purpose of paying royalties and license fees to third party providers, such as game developers and other copyright holders and content distributors; 
  * Ask you to participate in surveys about products, services, news and events; 
  * Offer you product upgrades, content, services and games for you to purchase; 
  * Provide you with content, services, instructions, and a more personalized experience based on personal information, such as your language preferences, zip/postal code, country locations, and any content or other preferences you provide; 
  * Auto-update downloaded MPP products; 
  * Provide you with news, free newsletters, updates, targeted advertising, promotions, and special offers; and 
  * Better understand how our products are used, including Web traffic patterns and what types of content are most popular with users of our products and services. 

#### WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?

MPP does not use your personal information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. MPP does not sell, rent, or share your personal information to a third party unless you consent to provide such information to a third party partner or content service. 

In some cases, access to certain products and services, such as content subscription products or products distributed by third parties, may require the provision of personal information to a third party, such as a content provider or distributor. In such cases, this will be stated during the registration process, in the terms of use, through the distribution process, or in a similar manner. The third party’s use of such information is governed by that party’s privacy policy, and MPP’s use is governed by this privacy policy. Please visit the privacy policy of the content partner to make sure you understand how they use the personal information you provide to them. If you do not wish for such a transfer to take place, you should not register for the applicable product or service. Additionally, MPP may be required to provide specific access and usage information to certain content providers and rights holders as a condition of content licensing and royalties. In such cases, MPP may provide content usage, access, demographic and other information without your personally identifiable information (your name, billing information, email address) to the content provider. 

MPP may disclose relevant information about our customers to our contractors (e.g. a customer service contractor or a credit card clearing service) in order for them to provide specific services for MPP, and to better serve our customers. MPP’s contractors are bound by strict contractual requirements to keep all personal information they process strictly confidential and to use such information solely on behalf of MPP. 

Also, MPP may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MPP; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MPP and its products; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MPP products or the public at large. 

MPP Websites and products contain links to other Websites and products. MPP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites or products. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices. 

##### Obligatory or Optional Nature of the Requested Information

Some of the personal information collected by MPP is necessary to provide you with the MPP product or service you choose and to optimize the delivery of data to your computer. MPP software may include the opportunity to disable certain software features to increase your level of privacy. However, certain technical information (e.g., zip code, product id, GUID) may be automatically transmitted between networked servers to authenticate access to products and services, enable their delivery, or optimize your media delivery experience. 

#### E-MAIL FROM MPOWERPLAYER

Registering for a product or service allows you to tell us how or whether you want MPP to communicate with you. Generally, we send e-mail to you about our products, content and special offers. Separate MPP products, services and lines of business may send separate newsletters and marketing emails. During registration, you may opt out of receiving MPP marketing e-mails and/or newsletters for the relevant product or service. However, we may continue to send you e-mail about products or services you have previously purchased (such as an available upgrade that you are entitled to receive), your account status or other information concerning functions, features and status of your MPP products and services, or to inform you about critical technical service issues relating to a MPP product or service. 

#### USE OF COOKIES

Like other major Websites, we use cookies to provide you with a tailored experience when visiting our Websites and using our products. We also use cookies to understand traffic patterns on MPP Websites and to authorize access to certain premium or trial content and product features. We treat any personal information that may be contained in cookies with the same level of confidentiality as other information you provide to us. 

MPP does not require that you accept cookies, however, some functionality on our Websites, our product purchase check-out process, and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with MPP products, services and Web pages. “Updated” may be used to alert users to recent changes and to the date of the last update. We also post FAQ’s from time to time on specific products. 

#### NON-US CUSTOMER INFORMATION

If you are a customer who is logging on from outside the United States, the personal information you submit to MPP will be sent to and stored in servers in the U.S. The personal information practices set out in this Privacy Policy apply to all MPP’s customers worldwide. 

#### NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE

We customarily release alpha and beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products generally, in all stages of release. MPP does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. MPP shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States. 

#### CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a complaint, please contact:

Privacy Policy Group  
Mpowerplayer, Inc.  
43480 Yukon Drive Suite 203  
Ashburn, VA 20147 USA
